The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
After the chaos in the royal capital had finally died down,
Asta and the Black Bulls were headed back home.
Look alive, knuckleheads. It's not that much farther now.
After all the crazy stuff that's happened,
it feels like we haven't been home in forever.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe I can have at least one day to work out in peace
before we get another job to do.
I'm not peaceful to you?
Huh?
Hey, look! Almost there!
メステータル
でも彼がて来るところはずだぜよねだー
そうだね。
俺大丈夫もだわない
料理が。
初ucchiniが増減奔 ciderか、
直接 hold up
Oh
We can catch the game
Don't lose
Look, don't lose
We can catch the game
I won't lose
Oh, yeah!
We're finally home!
Hey, Henry!
Hurry up and switch this puppy back to the way it was before!
What's the holdup, Henry?
Is something wrong?
You gassy?
What does the hideout look like?
I can't remember
What?
This guy's a freaking riot
What the hell?
Didn't you live here longer than anybody?
They'll walk you through it
First you come in and there's the living room, right?
And after that is...
You explain it to him, Asta
What? Who? Me?
No! I'm clueless here!
Next is my shrine to Marie
Actually, I'm pretty sure it was a giant pantry
with snacks from all over the kingdom in it
Nah, it was the sauna
Whoa, where did you guys live?
But maybe we did have a snack cabinet and a sauna
To be fair, the rooms were always shifting around
so it's kind of difficult to picture what went where
Well...
You guys kept breaking everything
Thanks for the years of free home repairs
but you didn't have to randomly change the whole floor plan
Without the help of my spatial magic
Captain Yami would have never found his way to the little boy's room
Think of all the awkward situations that could have been avoided
Sorry, everyone
Hey! Why don't we tell Henry everything we want in a hideout
and then he can put all of our ideas together
and make this building the coolest, comfiest place in the whole kingdom
Yeah, Asta, that's a killer idea
Sounds like a plan to me
As long as I can enjoy my drinks in the new place, I'm in
You're shooting for the moon, aren't you?
Home is the place where the greatest of friendships are forged
Alright, you morons, knock yourselves out
We'll do that, sir!
We're counting on you, Henry!
Leave it to me
Everybody take one
Write all the stuff you want on these forms
Can't forget you two
There's always a thing with you
Wow
He seems overwhelmed
Do you think we maybe asked too much of him?
My request was for the hideout to be relocated
so it's right next to the church where Marie lives
This is great!
Now I can see you every day!
Oh, Marie!
I can't wait to be your neighbor!
I am not too picky
as long as I get to be in the same room as all my friends
every second of every day
I've reached the pinnacle of embarrassment
so I want a place where I can hide away forever!
If I can be surrounded by dark curtains
I'll be more than happy, okay?
My dream is to live where I'm allowed to eat tenfold
Yeah, you already do that
Hey, how about we throw in an open bar, too?
I'm surrounded by idiots
Hey, guess what?
I requested a room that's right next door to yours, Magna
Which means that if I use my magic detection
I'll always be able to tell what you're doing
on the other side of the wall
I can't wait to mess with you
I'll knock your teeth out!
Go on and try!
Oh, say that again, you little turd!
Only next to me!
I guess if Nero gets moved into a different room
then she can't wake me up anymore
I was only pecking you so you would stop snoring so loudly
Hey, wait!
When Nero was in her bird form
she used to sleep in the same room as Asta!
I mean, to be fair, he didn't know she was a cute girl back then
She just perched on the windowsill, right?
Why do I even care in the first place?
Um...
Henry's really giving this a lot of thought, huh?
Well, it's important!
Alright, get back to work
What's all this stuff for?
You want us to go hunting for bugs or something?
Of course not, you idiot
My adorable little pets used to live here
before our hideout got wrecked by the eye of the midnight sun
so now they're running loose
Go track them down before they cause trouble
Sir!
Oh, I forgot about them!
It's no big deal, though
They got pretty used to me after I took care of them
I'm sure this is going to be a piece of cake
Don't count on that, kid
Huh?
These woods are their backyard
They probably went feral again after a couple of days
The second you let your guard down, they'll eat you alive
Hang on, if they're that scary
how come you're sending me out there with only this tiny net?
Quit your panicking and go get my pets back
There are three magical beasts
If the rest of you are bored, go help them
Okay!
Yes, sir! Dummy, sir!
It's going to be so much fun to spar with some magical beasts
If you lay even one finger on my precious babies, I'll rip you limb from lamb
Would you two leave me alone?
I'm trying to have a conversation with a photograph of my little sister
Our friends counting on us
I hope this won't end in total embarrassment
Are you listening to me?
You guys ready to go?
I think the three of us should team up since we're the squad rookies
If you say so
Wait, wasn't Zora here just a second ago?
No thanks
I've got better things to do
Oh well
That mask-wearing punk can bail if he wants
I'll just punish him later
I've got an important duty to attend to
Well, I'm leaving this up to you guys
Hey monsters!
Where are you?
That's actually kind of cute
Cute!
Do you really think that's going to work?
How stupid can you be?
Don't forget
The captain said they're probably feral
So if we act like bait, we'll just get mauled
I know, but I was the one who took care of them
So maybe they'll come to their senses when they realize who I am
Come to think of it, Nero
You were kind of like my pet back when you were in your bird form
So you understand what I mean, don't you?
You shouldn't patronize me
In my bird form, I was watching over your grimoire, not you
If you ask me, you were the pet
They say the more you argue, the closer you are
I mean, not that it makes any difference to me
I only came along because I have no choice in the matter
What's that key I'm sensing?
What?
Um, I don't know, but there was no way I was thinking about you two
Found ya!
Pasta!
What's this flock of antsy birds doing here?
They're about to pick me to dance!
They must be angry because you're so noisy
I'll see if I can locate them from the sky
Nero, save me!
Maybe I'm worried about nothing
Kind of seems like they hate each other
Wait, we're alone now?
Man, this place is freaking creepy
What's the matter? You scared?
What are you talking about? I'm not scared
Just shut your yap and put some pep in your step
Hey, I told you to hurry
That little snot probably hit somewhere so we could go
BOOM!
And try to spook me
Don't bother, Small Fry
I'll make you regret this
Did you think an amateur move like that would actually work on me?
No!
Aaaaaah!
My spear and shock plan was a huge success!
I'ma kill you!
I don't know!
Are you sure you can?
Well, there's nobody out here to make us stop fighting so feel free to come at me with everything you got!
Well, I wouldn't say that if I were you! Things have changed and you and I are on totally different levels these days!
That's for damn sure! You may not know this, but I developed unbelievable strength after our battle when you were possessed!
Oh really? That makes two of us then!
The mana's calling to me! I haven't sparred with you in ages! So I'll probably have too much fun and get carried away!
What are you waiting for?
Oh gosh! What was that loud sound?
Magna and Luck, I think they're reigniting their fiery friendship.
Who gives a crap?
And you two! How long do you plan on cowering behind me?
Please pretend I'm not here! This whole situation is so humiliating!
Then why didn't you just stay home?
Well, I wanted to, but there aren't any walls left to conceal my shame!
I'm not your damn wall!
This forest is really scary, and we're not sure when the magical beasts might attack.
Don't worry, your face is the most terrifying thing here!
Hey!
I wish you'd stop making eye contact with me!
Yep, there they are. The faster I wrangle these monsters, the sooner I can visit my sweet Marie.
You ready guys?
Hey, what the hell are you doing?!
I'm sorry, it's just that they popped up out of nowhere and it caused my embarrassment to evolve into pure terror!
But I can't do this. My heart's not ready to let me go.
Get off of me!
I can't believe I got teamed up with the two biggest scaredy-cats on the squad!
How am I supposed to catch these things with you two hanging on to me?!
Yum, this is so delicious! Nothing's better than snuffing down and be fun while you're hunting magical beasts!
I prefer a strong drink.
Hey, Finral, can you make a portal and go buy me another bottle or two?
Um, don't you guys think we should get back to hunting soon?
Oh, quit being a goody two-shoes and drink up, you big nerd!
You know you want to try some of these nummy treats, they're fresh out of the oven!
Listen, it's not that I don't want to, I just don't feel like it's a good idea!
If the captain found out, he'd kill me for sure!
Then again, I'm sure the others already caught them anyway, so there's no reason we can't relax for a little bit!
Hey, where'd Finral go?
So get me that drink!
By the way, do you have any more snacks, Charmy?
Have I had too many?
Oh my goodness, Charmy, you're so tall all of a sudden and so hairy too!
Not to mention those nails of yours, you're in desperate need of a manicure, you know?
Otherwise, that pretty boy from the Golden Dawn will never like you back!
That was a great fight! You've really improved!
Heh, back at ya. Just for now, I guess I can let you off the hook.
That said, you're not gonna leave me behind, do you understand me?
If you get ten times stronger than I will too. You might get a step ahead, but you'll never outdo me. I hope you're okay with that.
My bad! Sorry, I couldn't really hear your big speech over all the growling.
Aw, dammit, there's always something! Just give me a second to recover my mana and stamina and then I'll save you, I promise.
Okay, that sounds fair.
Hey, don't eat me! I'm the guy who used to take care of you before Austin came along! Don't tell me you forgot about me already! Come on, I swear I don't take that gun!
Geez, where could those things be?
Nero still hasn't come back either.
Being alone with him makes me jumpy.
Those are Magnus glasses!
It can't be! They ate him?
Look!
Oh man, are you guys okay?
Talk to us!
It's bad. The other Black Bulls were also defeated by the Magical Beasts.
Huh?
Asta, forget about us. Just run!
Captain Yomi! He's in trouble!
It's occupied.
Hey!
I'm in here, dammit!
Who is that?
Look, if you're good for nothing slackers are back already, then you better have my pets with you.
I'm up against a tough opponent here and if I don't concentrate he's gonna go back and hide each other.
Give me a minute!
Sheesh!
I'm glad the three of you are home, but you're probably not waiting in line to use the John, huh?
Captain Yomi's way stronger than we are, so he might be okay.
But Magna and Luck almost got eaten alive.
If all three attack him at once, I'm not sure if he'll make it.
Just hang in there, okay?
I'm on my way to rescue you!
Hey!
Stop licking me already, you big lugs!
Ugh!
Your drool smells like garbage!
What the heck, Captain Yomi?
I rushed over here to save you because I thought you were being attacked by the Magical Beast, but you're fine!
Well, I guess they technically did attack me.
They wanted some attention from you.
Come on, that's it?
Really?
These big fellas are always crazy affectionate.
In fact, they've been like that ever since I first met them.
I remember, I was on my way back to the hideout.
When I found them, the poor thing's parents had just been killed and they were all alone.
I guess some nobles were out hunting magical beasts for support.
Sorry, little ones.
You folks aren't ever gonna wake up again.
Look, I got separated from my parents too, but all we can do is chin up and keep on keeping on.
Hey, don't get the wrong idea.
I never said I was gonna take care of you.
How am I supposed to say no to that?
Oh, wow!
That was such a heartwarming story, sir!
I bet those beasts were so adorable and they were teeny weeny little babies!
How sweet.
Anyway, it didn't even take six months for these guys to grow up as big as their parents had been.
It cost me a fortune to keep them fed, so I keep trying to abandon them.
Okay, you just ruined it!
That's mean.
I sent you guys off to Catrum so they didn't wander into a nearby village and wreak havoc or anything like that.
Although, if it seemed like they wanted to return to the wild and be free,
I was kind of thinking of letting them loose in the mountains somewhere as soon as we could get a hold of them again.
Whee!
Hey, Captain Yami's still in one piece!
Magna, you're back!
I thought you were hurt real bad!
Nope.
But they did lick us all over, so we smell kinda ripe now.
It seemed like they were gonna gobble us up, but they just wanted us to pet them and play with them.
Apparently, it was enough to make everyone faint from exhaustion.
You're such a troublesome group.
Well, we figured if they were that excited to see us, then Captain Yami would have a really hard time fighting them off, so we were concerned for his safety!
But the boss man's A-OK!
I'm sure he's used to it. He is their owner, after all.
Who's a good magical beastie?
I better make some dolls of the three of you as well.
Don't lick Marie or you're dead.
They're pretty cute, but their drool smells like death.
If you want us to pet you some more, go take a bath and brush your teeth.
I see. They must love the rest of the Black Bulls just like they love the Captain!
Hey there! Since I'm your caretaker, do you want me to pet you for a while?
Judging by that look, they still think of you as dinner.
That can't be it! These guys totally adore me!
Here you go! I brought you a little snacky snack, but you gotta sit first!
This is hard to watch.
Hey, did I miss anything?
Zora! What have you been up to this whole time?
I don't see how that's your business, kid. The hideout's still not finished. The sun's going down.
Actually, it is. I just need to put it together.
Recombination magic. Black Bull's hideout. Hard Rock Bison style.
The outside was Magna's idea. So tacky.
You know, for a royal, you really don't know sophistication in class when you see them.
Sweet! I can't wait to look inside!
Oh, it's just what I wanted. This way I can drink to my heart's content.
I keep stuffing my face and the food never stops coming!
Why is there a giant hole in the floor?
I wanted a place where I could hide in the dark when I'm embarrassed, which is constantly...
I couldn't be Marie's neighbor, but this is still nice.
Hey, Angel Marie, tell Big Brother tomorrow's forecast, huh?
Mostly sunny, but partly cloudy. Temperatures will be mild during the day and a little chillier as night falls.
This talking Marie doll is incredible. Henry is a genius.
No cute maid, huh? Oh well.
I can clean your room for you.
No thanks!
Just an idea.
Uh, right. I appreciate the thought.
What about the rooms? Who's everyone paired up with?
I'm glad you asked. This part was Gordon's request.
We should all share the same room as friends.
What? So I'm not next door to Asta, I'm sharing a room with him? As friends? That's a step above friends, isn't it? This is crazy!
Kinda reminds me of sharing a space with Yuno and Nash at the church.
Man, this is gonna be a blast!
I'm not okay with this.
Neither am I.
Right, this isn't up to my royal standards.
So simple!
Well, I can't say I'm crazy about sharing a room with luck, but it'll be fun to stay up late chatting with Captain Yami every night.
Yeah, I'm gonna veto that right now.
Alright, I forgot. The captain's in a different room.
Seriously?
What the hell is this?
It was a request from the magic beasts.
Well, when you put it like that, I guess...
It's still a no!
That's better. We need a hideout.
We need a hideout, not a freaking amusement park.
That's why I made Henry change it back into the dusty old mansion it was when we started.
The wine fountain was nice, but it's a lot cozier this way.
Yeah, it's got that home sweet home feeling.
I'm definitely not disappointed at all. No way!
When I first walked into this hideout after becoming a black bull,
everyone accepted me right off the bat even though I didn't have any magic ability.
Ever since then, every day's been an adventure.
We had plenty of close calls, but it always turned out okay because they were here to help me.
You guys! There's something I need to say!
I'm really glad I joined the black bulls and met all of you!
Aw, what's making you get so sentimental all of a sudden?
I feel the same.
All of us have grown so much because you never gave up, Asta.
You're reckless and stubborn, but that's not a bad thing. Sometimes.
We need to hurry and clear Asta's name!
Yeah!
First things first, we better figure out everything we can about those devils.
Right!
Come on.
You're полностью there, too.
You're not even optimistic.
Come on!
You Entreли
You.
So now again, a generation flies around wind
Besides I was born,
I thought that's another story
A dazzling memory
Lightning
enas
There are no Heavy
The sea
居場所を示す足跡はやがて消えてしまうから
新しいページを今開こう
恐れずに先頭で旗を振ろう
向かいかす強いほど高くまで飛べるから
Just take my hand
今日を生きる君に
明日が待っている
バクローバー 第126
バルローゼスフェッション
バクローバー カットンシャルティングを
言い合受 long
バクローバー
ゲーム寺の欲しい